thrust.io 2016-03-08

# Privacy Policy | Anymail finder

We value the privacy of our customers, and we do everything in our power to protect it. By using our website, you agree to this Privacy Policy.

## Information we collect

When you visit our website and sign up for an account you might be asked to enter your name, email address, credit card information and other details to improve your experience and enable us to process your orders.

## How we protect your information

We do not use vulnerability scanning and/or scanning to PCI standards. We use regular Malware Scanning.

Your personal information is contained behind secured networks and is only accessible by a limited number of persons who have special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential. In addition, all sensitive/credit information you supply is encrypted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology.

We implement a variety of security measures when a user places an order enters, submits, or accesses their information to maintain the safety of your personal information.

All transactions are processed through a gateway provider and are not stored or processed on our servers.

## Usage of cookies

We use cookies to improve your experience and keep track of your session. We also use cookies to track your interaction with the website to improve its usability and decide how to improve the software.

We use Google Analytics to analyze how our visitors interact with our website.

If you'd like you can disable cookies on your browser (Instructions fo [IE](http://windows.microsoft.com/en-GB/internet-explorer/delete-manage-cookies), [Firefox](https://support.mozilla.org/en-US/kb/enable-and-disable-cookies-website-preferences), [Chrome](https://support.google.com/chrome/answer/95647?hl=en), [Safari](http://help.apple.com/safari/mac/8.0/#/sfri11471)).

## Third party disclosure

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information.

## Third party links

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

## CalOPPA provisions

Users can visit the website anonymously, and a link to to this Privacy Policy is included at the bottom of all pages on the site.

Users can change their personal information from the dashboard, and delete all records we have of you by emailing us.

## Do not track signals

We are not able to honor Do not track signals on our website as it would compromise the user experience.

## COPPA

When it comes to the collection of personal information from children under 13, the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA) puts parents in control. The Federal Trade Commission, the nation's consumer protection agency, enforces the COPPA Rule, which spells out what operators of websites and online services must do to protect children's privacy and safety online.

We do not specifically market to children under 13.

## Data breaches

We will notify the users via email within 7 business days.

We also agree to the individual redress principle, which requires that individuals have a right to pursue legally enforceable rights against data collectors and processors who fail to adhere to the law. This principle requires not only that individuals have enforceable rights against data users, but also that individuals have recourse to courts or a government agency to investigate and/or prosecute non-compliance by data processors.

## CAN-SPAM

We strictly follow the rules set out by the CAN-SPAM act. Specifically, we collect your email address in order to create your account and allow you to recover it if necessary. It is also used to send transactional emails (e.g. notifications of payments) and occasional newsletters. You'll be able to opt out of the latter.

## Changes

From time to time, we will change our Privacy Policy. We will update this page when we make changes to the privacy policy, and if a significant change is made, we will email our customers before the changes take effect.

## Contacting Us

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below.

Finest Venture Limited  
2 Sheraton St,  
London W1F 8BH,  
United Kingdom  
team@anymailfinder.com  
+44 20 3137 8715

LAST EDITED: AUGUST 25, 2015
